[
  {
    "question": "ich",
    "answer": "εγώ",
    "phonetic": "eg**o**"
  },
  {
    "question": "du",
    "answer": "εσύ",
    "phonetic": "es**i**"
  },
  {
    "question": "er",
    "answer": "αυτός",
    "phonetic": "aft**o**s"
  },
  {
    "question": "sie (feminin)",
    "answer": "αυτή",
    "phonetic": "aft**i**"
  },
  {
    "question": "wir",
    "answer": "εμείς",
    "phonetic": "em**i**s"
  },
  {
    "question": "ihr",
    "answer": "εσείς",
    "phonetic": "es**i**s"
  },
  {
    "question": "sie (plural)",
    "answer": "αυτοί",
    "phonetic": "aft**i**"
  },
  {
    "question": "leben",
    "answer": "ζωή",
    "phonetic": "zo**i**"
  },
  {
    "question": "haus",
    "answer": "σπίτι",
    "phonetic": "sp**i**ti"
  },
  {
    "question": "stadt",
    "answer": "πόλη",
    "phonetic": "p**o**li"
  },
  {
    "question": "apfel",
    "answer": "μήλο",
    "phonetic": "m**i**lo"
  },
  {
    "question": "äpfel",
    "answer": "μήλα",
    "phonetic": "m**i**la"
  },
  {
    "question": "sonne",
    "answer": "ήλιος",
    "phonetic": "**i**lios"
  },
  {
    "question": "wasser",
    "answer": "νερό",
    "phonetic": "ner**o**"
  },
  {
    "question": "ich bin",
    "answer": "είμαι",
    "phonetic": "**i**me"
  },
  {
    "question": "ich spreche",
    "answer": "μιλάω",
    "phonetic": "mil**a**o"
  },
  {
    "question": "ich verstehe",
    "answer": "καταλαβαίνω",
    "phonetic": "katalav**e**no"
  },
  {
    "question": "der mann",
    "answer": "ο άντρας",
    "phonetic": "o **a**ndras"
  },
  {
    "question": "die frau",
    "answer": "η γυναίκα",
    "phonetic": "i yin**e**ka"
  },
  {
    "question": "die männer",
    "answer": "οι άντρες",
    "phonetic": "i **a**ndres"
  },
  {
    "question": "die frauen",
    "answer": "οι γυναίκες",
    "phonetic": "i yin**e**kes"
  },
  {
    "question": "das kind",
    "answer": "το παιδί",
    "phonetic": "to ped**i**"
  },
  {
    "question": "jetzt",
    "answer": "τώρα",
    "phonetic": "t**o**ra"
  },
  {
    "question": "morgen",
    "answer": "αύριο",
    "phonetic": "**a**vrio"
  },
  {
    "question": "gestern",
    "answer": "χθες",
    "phonetic": "chthes"
  },
  {
    "question": "schön",
    "answer": "ωραίος",
    "phonetic": "or**e**os"
  },
  {
    "question": "gut",
    "answer": "καλός",
    "phonetic": "kal**o**s"
  },
  {
    "question": "wie",
    "answer": "πώς",
    "phonetic": "pos"
  },
  {
    "question": "warum",
    "answer": "γιατί",
    "phonetic": "yiat**i**"
  },
  {
    "question": "wo",
    "answer": "πού",
    "phonetic": "pou"
  }
]
